NEHA BAGUL

Mobile number: 9399900421, Email I'd: nehabagul4@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

Driven and well-organized HR and Sales profile with 10+ years of experience. Helping in employers' recruitment and retain qualified candidates. Skilled at partnering with management teams to build employee-centric cultures promoting positive morale and optimizing productivity. Motivating to employees with positive attitude, and also try to conducting market research to identify selling possibilities and evaluate customer needs. Actively seeking out new sales opportunities through cold calling, networking and social media. Meetings with potential clients and listening to their wishes and concerns.

WORK HISTORY

07.2023 - Currently Working Dhorajia Projects LLP & Dhorajia Construction Pvt.Ltd

HR Manager

- Managing the recruitment and selection process
- Develop and implement HR strategies and initiatives aligned with the overall business strategy
- Bridge management and employee relations by addressing demands, grievances or other issues
- Support current and future business needs through the development, engagement, motivation and preservation of human capital
- Develop and monitor overall HR strategies, systems, tactics and procedures across the organization
- Oversee and manage a performance appraisal system that drives high performance
- Report to management and provide decision support through HR metrics
- Ensure legal compliance throughout human resource management

01.2022 - 05.2023 KONCEPTWISE DIGITAL MEDIA PVT.LTD

HR specialist & B.D.M - Konceptwise Digital Media Pvt.Ltd Ahmedabad

- Coordination with Top Management and understanding their requirements, defining job positions and Approvals.
- Conducting telephone and Personal interviews in coordination with Management
- Manage employee life cycle like joining to exit formality for all the levels.
- Handling all admirative work for employee data management
- Maintaining employee's personal files and records, communicating HR policies & across the organization at all levels.
- Developing employee engagement programs like Initiated and administered a welcome all new joiners, Initiated regular Birthday celebration and Monthly performance and festival celebrations.
- Researching, planning, and implementing new target market initiatives
- Developing quotes and proposals for prospective clients
- Understand the target markets, including industry, company, project, company contacts and which market strategies can be used to attract clients
- Follow the latest industry developments and stay up-to-date on corporate competitors
- Act as account manager for Customer to provide them with solution and support related to the services

10.2021 -01.2022 CROWN PLAZA HOTEL JAIPUR

Club Coordinator - Crown Plaza Hotel Jaipur

- Answer telephones and respond to inquiries from clients and participants
- Take reservations for booths and speaking engagements
- Promote brand image and awareness through social media
- Form contacts with local media outlets, both online and offline
- Answer potential clients' questions about facility and amenities
- Take reservation for our all restaurants in the behalf of our exacting and new clients

HR EXECUTIVE- RMI MOTORS PVT. LTD.

- Coordination with Top Management and understanding their requirements, defining job positions and Approvals.
- Resourcing, screening and short listing resumes through various job portals or else internal reference.
- Conducting telephone and Personal interviews in coordination with department heads.
- Preparing offer letter, employment contract and job descriptions, completing joining Formalities and documentation.
- Maintaining employees' personal files and records, communicating HR policies & across the organization at all levels.
- Preparation of full and final settlement generation of Experience Letters.
- Celebrations Diwali, Ganpati Festival, and other company events
- Effectively managing welfare measures, management employee get together, picnics & parties.
- Developing employee engagement programs like Initiated and administered a welcome-mail policy to all new joiners, Initiated regular Birthday mailers & celebration policy

05.2016 - 12.2018

JAIPUR MARRIOTT HOTEL, JAIPUR

Sales Coordinator- Marriott Jaipur

- Drove customer satisfaction advocacy through communication and relationship management.
- Convert leads to visits and convert visits to bookings.
- Coordinate with caterer and decorator to ensure all commitments are delivered.
- Maintain a good relationship with venue owners and other stakeholders Advise Liaising with external customers, to anticipate and respond to their needs.

09.2015 - 04.2016

SURJEET HYUNDAI, BHOPAL

HR EXECUTIVE- SURJEET HYUNDAI

- Handle Recruitment, Screen, Interview, hire and exit of employees.
- Maintain the records of employees.
- Track out the daily attendance of the employees.
- Effectively managing welfare measures management employee get together, picnics and Parties
- Developing employee engagement programs like- Initiated and administered a Welcome mail Policy to all new joiners, initiated regular birthday mailers and celebration party.
- Connect with employees on daily basis so that their problems can be resolved

04.2014 - 08.2015

Courtyard Marriott, Bhopal

SALES COORDINATOR- MARRIOTT BHOPAL

- I was responsible for making sales calls with peoples, creating new leads and add fresh customers and handling customers with their queries
- Planning & preparing monthly for monthly targets
- Maintain a good relationship with venue owners and other stakeholders.
- Convert leads to visits and convert visits to bookings Verification

INSURANCE EXECUTIVE & COMPUTER OPERATOR- MY CAR BHOPAL

- Handling customers with their queries.
- Contact potential clients and create rapport by networking.
- Cold calling, using referrals etc. Convert leads to visits and convert visits to bookings.
- Sales calls with customers for selling of Car insurance policy.
- Retain continuous awareness of transactions, sales and terms and keep relative records

EDUCATION

2012	Rajiv Gandhi Collage - Bhopal B.com Bachelor of commerce	
2009	Naveen Girls H.S School Bhopal Higher Secondary Higher secondary	
2006	Naveen Girls H.S School Bhopal Higher secondary Higher School	

EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITES

- Winner of Taekwondo competition at State level in school.
- Winner of Singing competition at State level in school.
- Star performer of the month twice

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth: 3rd December 1989 Languages: Hindi, English

Place: Ahmedabad Neha Bagul